My first ever PT client
was a chiropractor,
and I got to experience one of
the most beautiful sales cycles ever.
So I went to the chiropractor because I
had a bad back, and every person that goes
in the chiropractor has a bad back.
No one goes there for a checkup.
No one just turns up going, "Hey,
can you check out my vertebrae?" So
straight
away, the second you walk in,
they're like, "We got you." So you go in,
and it's
not just enough to say,
"I've got a bad back." They go,
"Let's do an X-ray." And
they get the X-ray, and they come out
and they go,
[inhales] "It's going to be 100
bucks for the X-ray, by the way,
just to let you know."
And then they put it up and
they go, "Oh, see this?
That's a bit of a L3 degeneration.
Those discs, a little bit close together.
Robert, how old are you? What, 36?
Oh,
this looks more like the disc degeneration
of a 55-year-old man." They just
depress you vertebrae by vertebrae,
and then afterwards they go, "But there
is a
remedy.
Come see me twice a week for an
adjustment." But the level of pain, they
don't just tell you, they show you.
And you already have the pain.
You're in there with a bad back,
but they try and make it seem out to be so
much
worse. And then just before you think,
"I'm going to be in a wheelchair for the
rest of my life," here's the solution.
They have to be some of the best
salespeople ever.